dealsupdate.in 2018-10-20

# Privacy Policy - Deals Update

Sridhar built the Online Deals & Offers India app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Sridhar at no cost and  
is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information  
if anyone decided to use my Service.

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The  
Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information  
with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Online  
Deals & Offers India unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable  
information. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

**Log Data**

I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information  
(through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device  
Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing  
my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to  
your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device’s internal memory.

This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use  
“cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies  
and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use  
some portions of this Service.

**Service Providers**

I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

  * To facilitate our Service;
  * To provide the Service on our behalf;
  * To perform Service-related services; or
  * To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is  
to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information  
for any other purpose.

**Security**

I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means  
of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100%  
secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links to Other Sites**

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note  
that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these  
websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any  
third-party sites or services.

**Children’s Privacy**

These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information  
from children under 13. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately  
delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with  
personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes.  
I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately  
after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me.

Rating: 5.0/ **5** (2 votes cast)

Privacy Policy, 5.0 out of 5 based on 2 ratings
